A large part of working with data is being able to
يتمحور جزء كبير من العمل مع البيانات حول القدرة
interpret data visualizations and explain your insights to others.
على تفسير عروض البيانات المرئية وشرح أفكارك للأخرين.
To give you some practice with this,
ولمساعدتك على التمرن على هذا،
I've selected three Tableau dashboards for you to explore.
قمت باختيار ثلاث لوحات معلومات من Tableau لتستطلعها.
Choose one of these three dashboards,
اختر إحدى اللوحات الثلاث،
whichever one interests you most,
أيها تثير اهتمامك أكثر،
and find three insights in the visualizations.
وجِد ثلاث معلومات مفيدة في العرض المرئي.
Write a short report explaining
قم بكتابة تقرير قصير تشرح فيه
each observation and how you found
كل ملاحظة وكيف وجدت المعلومات
The first dashboard has population characteristics about the city of Madrid.
تحتوي لوحة المعلومات الأولى على الخصائص السكانية لمدينة "مدريد".
It will interact with you as you scroll and click through it.
وستتفاعل اللوحة معك خلال تنقلك فيها والنقر عليها.
You can gain information about each specific part of the city in terms of births,
يمكنك اكتساب المعلومات حول كل جزء محدد من المدينة فيما يخص الولادات
deaths, and additional info.
والوفيات ومعلومات اضافية.
The second dashboard shows the impact of
تعرض لوحة المعلومات الثانية
malaria in different regions of Africa year-over-year.
تأثير مرض الملاريا في مناطق مختلفة من "أفريقيا" سنة بعد سنة.
This, too, is interactive and allows you to
هذه اللوحة أيضاً تفاعلية وتسمح لك
view trends and the number of deaths for different regions.
باستعراض الاتجاهات وعدد الوفيات في مناطق مختلفة.
The final dashboard shows the top skills according to LinkedIn in 2016 for each country.
تعرض اللوحة الأخير أفضل المهارات وفقاً لمنصة LinkedIn في عام 2006 لكل بلد.
These skills are also ranked globally,
هذه المهارات مصنفة إلى رتب عالمياً أيضاً،
where one is considered to be the best ranking.
حيث المهارة ذات الرتبة "1" تُعد المهارة الفضلى.
For your final project,
في مشروعك الأخير
you will be building dashboards just like these to
ستبني لوحات معلومات كهذه تماماً 00:01:15,409 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 لمشاركة معلوماتك المفيدة حول مجموعة بياناتك الخاصة.